<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fragments_1</string>
    <string name="text_email">E-mail</string>
    <string name="text_enter_you_address">Enter you address</string>
    <string name="text_password">Password</string>
    <string name="text_enter_you_password">Enter you password</string>
    <string name="text_accept_user_agreement">Accept user agreement</string>
    <string name="text_login">Login</string>
    <string name="text_arm_button">ARM Button</string>
    <string name="text_incorrect_input">Incorrect login or password</string>
    <string name="text_about_pineapple">How about a delicious slice of freshly cut sweet and slightly tangy pineapple, sounds delightful, right! Well ,this amazing fruit has certainly made its way to various culinary innovations right from amping up the taste quotient of mocktails to desserts to adding a hint of taste to exotic meat recipes, pineapple is a not just a fruit, but is an experience. Most pineapple lovers indulge in this amazing fruit because of its drool-worthy taste and enchanting aroma, but did you know that this amazing delight has a lot more to offer! Pineapple is scientifically known as Ananas comosus. Not only is this fruit delicious, but at the same time it has some incredible health benefits that will simply take your love for this fruit by a notch. So, read on to know more about pineapples. Amazing health benefits of pineapple This wonder fruit traces its origin to South America. However, it was later explored by the Europeans and was named as pineapple due to its similarity to the pinecone. Enriched with the goodness of nature, this tropical fruit is a rich source of antioxidants and enzymes, which are essential in curing several diseases. What\'s More, pineapples are a powerhouse of nutrition. Right from boosting immunity, aiding in digestion, to being a dose of nutrients such as vitamins A, B, C, potassium, manganese, this wonder food makes for a perfect food for good health. Here are a few incredible health benefits of this wonder fruit: Boosts immunity Pineapple is a great source of vitamin C, antioxidants, enzymes and fiber, which helps in proper functioning of the body. Moreover, the presence of vitamin C helps in fighting cell damage and prevents joint pain and coronary diseases. Strengthens your bones Loaded with the goodness of manganese, which helps in improving bone mineral density and strengthens the bones. Pineapple helps in preventing osteoporosis in women. According to a study, daily consumption of this fruit helps in improving bone health. Helps in treating cold and cough Pineapple is a great source of vitamin C and bromelain, which helps in reducing cough causing mucus in the throat and nasal cavity. Due to its anti-inflammatory properties, it helps in curing colds and cough. Helps in treating injuries The presence of bromelain helps in reducing swelling and helps reduce loss of blood byu promoting coagulation of the blood. So, adding pineapple to your diet can help in treating these basic ailments and injuries. Reduces stress Not only is this fruit delicious, but at the same time it can lift up your mood with its taste and aroma. Moreover, they contain a good level of B vitamins which improves your brain health. And helps in better functioning of the brain and boosts your ability to deal with stress efficiently.</string>


</resources>